# Yuqing Zhu

yuqingzhu@ucsb.edu https://jeremy43.github.io/

#### RESEARCH INTERESTS

My research interest is machine learning, including differential privacy [1-9] and domain adaptation [6, 8]. I am also the co-creator of AutoDP, an open-source library that allows researchers to use advanced mechanisms in differential privacy and obtain strong guarantees correctly.

#### **EDUCATION**

# University of California, Santa Barbara

2018.09- 2023.10 (expected)

Ph.D. in Computer Science

Nanjing University

2014.09-2018.06

B.S in Computer Science National Elite Program

#### AWARDS

2021 Google PhD Fellowship Recipient

#### PUBLICATION AND PREPRINT

- [1] Rachel Redberg, **Yuqing Zhu**, Yu-Xiang Wang. Generalized PTR: User-Friendly Recipes for Data-Adaptive Algorithms with Differential Privacy. In AISTATS-2023 (Oral presentation)
- [2] **Yuqing Zhu**, Yu-Xiang Wang. Adaptive Private-K-Selection with Adaptive K and Application to Multi-label PATE. In AISTATS-2022.
- [3] Yuqing Zhu, Jinshuo Dong, Yu-Xiang Wang. Optimal Accounting of Differential Privacy via Characteristic Function. In AISTATS-2022.
- [4] Chong Liu, **Yuqing Zhu**, Kamalika Chaudhuri and Yu-Xiang Wang. *Revisiting Model-Agnostic Private Learning: Faster Rates and Active Learning*. In AISTATS-2021 and the Journal of Machine Learning Research-2021.
- [5] **Yuqing Zhu** and Yu-Xiang Wang. Improving Sparse Vector Technique with Renyi Differential Privacy. In NeurIPS-2020.
- [6] **Yuqing Zhu**, Xiang Yu, Manmohan Chandraker, Yu-Xiang Wang. *Private-kNN: Practical Differential Privacy for Computer Vision*. In CVPR-2020.
- [7] Yuqing Zhu and Yu-Xiang Wang. Poisson Subsampled Renyi Differential Privacy. In ICML-2019.
- [8] Yuqing Zhu, Chong Liu and Yu-Xiang Wang. *Model-Agnostic Private Learning with Domain Adaptation*. In CSS Theory and Practice of Differential Privacy Workshop (TPDP-2020).
- [9] **Yuqing Zhu**, Xiang Yu, Yi-Hsuan Tsai, Francesco Pittaluga, Masoud Faraki, Manmohan chandraker, Yu-Xiang Wang. *Voting-based Approaches For Differentially Private Federated Learning*. In International Workshop on Federated Learning (FL-NeurIPS-2022).

#### RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

## Google Research NYC

2022.06 - 2022.09

Advisor: Matthew Joseph, Kareem Amin (Privacy team)

New York

· Investigated amplification by sampling in differentially private statistics release with c++ implementations in Google products.

## Google Research Seattle

2021.06 - 2021.09

Advisor: Shanshan Wu and Galen Andrew (Federated Learning Team)

WFH

· Investigated weighting approaches in differentially private federated learning.

#### **NEC Laboratories America**

Advisor: Xiang Yu (Media Analytics)

2020.06 - 2020.09

San Jose, CA

· Differentially private federated learning

Proposed a voting-based solution for differentially private federated learning. See Publication [6, 9].

### Microsoft Research Asia

2017.06 - 2017.11

Advisor: Jifeng Dai (Visual Computing Group)

MSRA, Beijing, China

· Video Instance-aware segmentation

Created an Official Implementation for Flow-Guided-Feature-Aggregation, and the git repo has already accumulated **500 stars**.github

LAMDA Lab

2016.05 - 2017.09

Advisor: Prof. Wu-Jun LI, Prof. Zhi-Hua Zhou

NJU, Nanjing, China

· Proposed a deep discrete hybrid recommendation system for image & text recommendation.

## ACADEMIC SERVICE

Reviewer: NeurIPS-22, ICML-22, NeurIPS-21, AISTATS-21, ICLR-20, ICML-20, ICML-19, UAI-19, NeurIPS-19

## TECHNICAL SKILLS

Computer Languages

Python, C++, Matlab

Deep Learning Frameworks

Pytorch/Tensorflow/MXNet/Caffee